Hello Hello,
Здравствуйте
I see you in
Здравствуйте я так вижу вас флаг такой в
this Orthodox flag.
этот православный
Yes, of course I see you, you are still a Tsar, you are a Tsar, a
Да конечно я вижу вас еще царь вы царь
Tsar admirer, so
царь почитатель так
not in general people, how do you feel about
не Вообще людей как вы относитесь к
this? I wonder how you feel about the fact
этому Интересно как вы относитесь тому
that Lenin, these communists overthrew the
что Ленин вот эти коммунисты скинули
Tsar, all sorts of
царя всякие
bad things, yes, why Russia then
плохо да А почему Россия тогда
it turns out that Lenin is held in high esteem in the
получается Ленина так в почете держат в
mausoleum
мавзолей
[music]
[музыка]
you have the corpse of Lenin in the mausoleum
у вас лежит труп Ленина мавзолей
But it works out and what’s more, we
Но это получается и больше того у нас
get it look at all these excursions
получается смотрите эти все экскурсии
so they go like worship, from the
так они идут Как поклонение вроде с
point of view of Christianity, worshiping
точки зрения христианства поклонения
the dead, so he was the Antichrist  he
мертвому вот и он антихрист был он
generally denied religion, he
вообще отрицал религию
realized how
понял А как
little it
мало
just somehow turns out to be combined in Russia now, and
просто как-то получается в России сейчас
this is the Soviet
совмещается и вот это Советская власть
imperial power, everything is so mixed up in a bunch,
имперская все так намешалось кучу
also so many Orthodox Christians
тоже столько столько православных
destroyed
уничтожил
[music]
[музыка]
and how do you feel about Putin
а как вы относитесь к Путину
? No, he’s not calling but  they didn’t find him, but he’s
Да нет он не зови но не застали но он
just loyal to everything
просто лоялен ко всему
Putin is for the Tsar or for Lenin
Путин за царя или за Ленина
Yes Putin As he says that Lenin was a
Да Путин Как говорит что Ленин был
villain and that they killed the Tsar and made
злодеем что да что убили царя сделали
a revolution
революцию
and you get it, it
а вы получаете
just turns out for me somehow I
просто получается для меня как-то я
see he takes it Before, he seemed to
смотрю он он берет Раньше он там вроде
be there  Putin is all for the Tsar, and here
как был за царя Путин все а тут начинает
Lenin begins, Stalin even turns out he is
вот Ленин Сталина даже получается он
resurrecting these
воскрешает вот эти
Soviet ideas of atheism. Look,
советские идеи безбожничества
democratic ones, here you are, let’s say in
демократические вот вы допустим в
America. By the way, I saw in America, I don’t
Америке Я кстати в Америке видел не
remember in which state on May 9 the
помню каком штате на 9 мая одеты
old Soviet uniforms are worn and people there walk around with these
старой формы и там люди ходят с этими
words
словами
I  I see that, for example,
Я смотрю что например
in Russia Lenin Stalin is revered there,
в России там почитается Ленин Сталин вот
these are the communists who fought against the Faith.
эти коммунисты которые боролись с Верой
And for example, Denikin and Kolchak. Why were
А например деникин да Колчак Почему их
n’t they reburied near the Kremlin
не перезахоронили возле Кремлевской
wall, for example
стены например
[music]
[музыка]
historical land to show that
историческую землю показать что
What do you think now, for example, Putin
А как вы считаете сейчас например Путин
is pursuing a policy of multiplication  of the
ведет политику на приумножение
Russian people or to decrease
российского народа или на уменьшение
[music]
[музыка]
I saw statistics that the Russians are dying out.
Я видел статистику что русский вымирают
And for example, it’s not the Russians who are reproducing
А например не русские размножаются
for whom you mean the Russians. Well,
за кого вы имеете ввиду русского Ну
look. For example, if we look Yes, in the
смотрите Например если мы смотрим Да в
Russians, in the Russians,
русский в русских
that you have a
что у вас
grandfather, I have paws
дед у меня лапы
No, I’m correct, I’m looking Here  now
Не ну я правильно я смотрю Вот сейчас
Russians Yes, for example, Russians are dying out
русские Да например русский вымирают
Russia Russians in Russia are worth less
Россия русских в России стоит все меньше
and less
и меньше
and the population of Russia is declining Russian
и население России сокращается русский
people Russian
человек
Who is Russian
русский Это кто русский
Bagration Bagration heard no I do
Багратион Багратиона слышали нет
n’t know Tatar you
не знаю татарин
don’t know I’m now a little dedicated
не знаете вот Я сейчас немножко посвящен
to Georgia, super he invested his life for Russia and
Грузии супер он жизнь вложил за Россию и
always spoke  that I’m Russian, a ton of
всегда говорил что я русский тонна
Georgians, Russian, and
грузин русский да
a person
человек
who doesn’t allow
который не дает топтать
his ancestors to be trampled on, the achievements of his ancestors.
своих предков достижения своих предков
That is,
То есть получается
I understand correctly that this is not a
я правильно понимаю что это не
nationality.
национальность
years ago This is what is
когда-то тысяч лет назад Вот это и
held together by such a bond that wants to
держится такая скрепы которые хотят
destroy Well, you said that Kadyrov is
разрушить Ну вы сказали что Кадыров
Russian
русский
Kadyrov is a Muslim, he
Кадыров мусульманин он православной
has an Orthodox bond and has nothing.
скрепки ничего не имеет
You are right to glorify God, it is wrong to
вы правильно славить Бога неправильно
glorify God. They read that
славят Бога Они читали
all Muslims are also Russian, it turns out
все мусульмане тоже русские получается
Regardless Where they live here, not for example
Независимо Где живут сюда не например
there, Morocco is all Russian  were I
там Марокко это все русские были я
say I say the Russian people the Russian
говорю я говорю русский народ русский
people were once cemented by Orthodoxy and the
народ скрепила когда-то православие и
Russian people do not divide people by
русский человек не делит людей
nationality into religion,
национальность на вероисповедание
our most recent one was not very
у нас самый последний не был очень
famous
известный
return everything That is, it turns out that I understood everything, it
возврата все То есть получается все
turns out look you, I
понял то получается смотрите ты я
understand correctly that Kadyrov is Russian
правильно понимаю что Кадыров русский
No, well  What do you think, but is he Russian or
Не ну вы как считаете но он русский или
not Russian? He is on business. So you are fussing about him,
не русский он по делам Вот вы его суете
he is Russian.
он русский
Hitler determined that he is not Russian. But
Гитлер определили что он не русский А
Kadyrov is Russian or not Russian,
Кадыровым русский или не русский
you said that Hitler was
вы сказали что Гитлер был
Kadyrov,
Кадыров
too, like he fought against the Russians. Kadyrov
тоже типа воевал против русских Кадырова
fought against the Russians in the first and second
воевал против русских в первой и второй
weeks
недели
why he says Chechens yes he says
почему он говорит чеченцы да говорит
because we are Muslims he says he
потому что мы мусульмане он говорит
shares you Orthodox
делит вы православные
[music]
[музыка]
Russia he turns out Russian too
России он тоже русский получается
Well you have to ask him And who is Russian
Ну надо у него спросить А кто русский
then I can’t You have to ask everyone
тогда я не могу У всех надо спрашивать
Burn out the staples I gave you an example I
выжглите скрепы Я вам пример я вам
gave you an example  you can read Can you give
пример это дал можете почитать А можете
me examples of Russians, give me examples of
мне примеры русских назовите примеры
Russians
русских
I can name examples not Russian not
я могу примеры назвать не русский не
Russians I myself can name a bunch
русских я сам могу назвать куча
Kadyrov is
Кадыров
not Russian he betrayed his ancestors Well
не русский он предал своих предков Ну
Kadyrov betrayed his
Кадыров предал свой
handed over his ancestors to the Chechens before and is
передал своих предков чеченцев до и
now working for a Russian on Putin
работает сейчас на русского на Путина
Putin was not Russian they
Путин не русский
killed  Russians he’s like now for them
убивали россиян он типа сейчас за них
and look you can name examples of
а смотреть можете назвать примеры
Russian examples
русского примерами
in general he called for killing the more
вообще призывал убивать чем больше
Russians as many as
Русских столько сколько
Heat of Khudaev and a
Жара худаев да
traitor to Russia
предателем России
he on the contrary is a hero of his people he’s a hero of
он наоборот герой своего народа он герой
his people he’s against the occupiers of
своего народа он противо оккупантов
Russia
России
Cool But you can still name an
Прикольно А можете все-таки назвать
example of a Russian
пример русского
you can give examples  Russian Pushkin Russian
можете примеры русского Пушкин русский
understood why he was Russian
понял чем он русский
and not Russian in Spirit
и по Духу не русский
[music]
[музыка]
Yes, the last one was very tired Count the
Да последняя сильно утомил Посчитай
books
книжки
after the last book by Yan who
после последнюю книжку Яна которые
wrote this is called
написал это называется
intellectual disorders of Russians on
интеллектуальные расстройства Россиян на
religious grounds,
религиозной почве
you can still give an example of a Russian
то можете все-таки пример русского
just look I dream of books
привести просто смотрите я мечтаю книжки
Just say  example of at least one
Скажите просто пример хоть одного
modern Russian who is modern
русского современного кто современный
Russian
русский
Prigozhin is Russian,
Пригожин русский
so I understood who else the guy is Russian
так понял кто еще чувак русский
or not
или нет
[music]
[музыка]
he is Russian
он русский
I think that Prigozhin is Russian Russian shooters
Я думаю что Пригожин русский стрелков
of course I got it super How did it happen
конечно Понял супер А как так получилось
that in the state of Russia such great
что в государстве России таких великих
Russian people as Prigozhin are shot down in an
русских людей как Пригожин сбивают в
airplane  before such great Russian people
самолете до таких великих русских людей
as shooters are sent to prison
как стрелков садят в тюрьму
I just don’t know maybe myself Maybe
Я просто я не знаю может сам Может у
his ass exploded there in the toilet
него пердак взорвался там в туалете
And here’s the question Jesus was Russian,
А еще вот вопрос Иисус был русский
do you think
вот Как вы считаете
he’s not Russian so he’s
он не русский так
not Russian [
не русский
music] yes
[музыка]
yes
да да
I understand correctly  what turns out
Я правильно понимаю что получается
the proceeds
выручки
were burnt You are Russian Russian yes And what do
подгорела Ты русский русский да А что у
you have God is not Russian
тебя Бог не русский получается
So you said that he is a Judas you said that
Так вы сказали что он иуде вы сказали
people you said that Jesus of people
что люди вы сказали что Иисус людей
then Jesus is not Russian
то Иисус он не русский
No he is not Russian And when did the Russians
Нет он не русский А когда русские
appear and when did the Russians
появились
appear then that's it  if
а когда появились русские тогда вот если
when there were no Russians, when the Russians
когда был русских не было когда
appeared, Tsarina
появились русские
Katerina was Russian, she
царица Катерина была русская
can’t because I give you questions
не может потому что я тебе даю вопросы
that knock you out and you immediately
которые тебя выбивают и ты сразу
sit on the core of your inner
садишься на стержень внутренней
look, Tsarina Katerina, yes, say Yes,
смотри царица Катерина да скажи Да царит
Tsarina Katerina reigns Tell her Who was her
царица Катерина Скажи она Кто была по
nationality, she was a Russian
национальности она была русская
German  So cool, that is, it turns out I’m
немка Так прикольно то есть получается я
right. I understood correctly that the Germans
правильно Я правильно понял что немцы
ruled correctly, the Germans ruled and she was for the
правильно немцы правили а она была за
faith.
веру
I can’t understand why Kadyrov is Russian
Я не могу понять почему Кадыров русский
and Tsarina Katerina is not Russian,
а царица Катерина не русская
she had favorites who were so
там у нее были фавориты которые так
absorbed,
впитывали
she was Russian or not Russian, after all.
она все-таки была русская или не русская
she was German, that
она была немка
is, not Russian,
то есть не русская
that is, she
то есть она получается да получается
turns out, yes it turns out, look that Hitler was A understood, understood Cool, and
А понял понял Прикольно
Kadyrov is Russian, I am from Ukraine, and Kadyrov is
а Кадыров он русский я Украине а Кадыров
Russian or not a Russian
русский или не русский
Jew by nationality
еврей по национальности
and that yes,
и что да
like Hitler, you want to kill you
как Гитлер вы хотите убивать
want you want to kill  Zelensky’s
вы хотите вы хотите убить Зеленского
influence itself, let’s
самого влияния
listen, let’s
слушай давай
say whether you’re Russian in spirit or not. I’ve been driving you so beautifully. In short, let’s finish this Kadyrov No, you said he’s Russian or he’s not
Нет ты говорил то он русский то не
Russian, come on, after all, you decide whether
русский давай все-таки Ты определись
Kadyrov is Russian or not Russian, that the
Кадыров русский или не русский что
final point on which they set
финальную точку по которому поставили
the task is question
задач вопрос
A  why didn’t you say Ask Katerina
А почему ты не сказал Спроси у Катерина
about Katerina said
про катерину сказал
wait you didn’t say Ask
подожди ты же не сказал Спроси у
Katerina you said
Катерины ты сказала
good to yourself And you read so many holes
про себя хорошо А ты читал столько дырок
you think you
ты считаешь
know
знаете
the 10 commandments
10 заповедей
and well, name the 10
и ну назови 10
commandments
заповедей
I am the Lord your God and there are no gods except
я Господь Бог твой и нет богов кроме
me this is the first Yes  second Don’t make yourself an
меня это первый Да вторая Не делай себе
idol 3 don’t say do
кумира 3 не произноси
n’t peek at the
не подглядываешь
camera look at the camera look Yes
камеру смотри в камеру смотри Да
read into the camera look at the camera you read
читай в камеру смотри камеру ты читаешь
you look away
ты глаза отводишь
at the camera Look and says
в камеру Смотри и говорит
I’m writing to you Liski to
Я пишу тебе Лиски чтобы
look at me like that and say 10
смотри так на меня да и говорю 10
I said on the line
я сказал на связи
you’re not  named the 10 commandments and
ты не назвал 10 заповедей да
further
дальше
This is what the Orthodox don’t know
Вот это православный не знает
Okay, learn the 10 commandments Come, let’s
Ладно выучить 10 заповедей Приходи давай
Damn the skills in short, find Russia all sorts of
Блин скильки короче найти России всякие
gouging the elevator just In short, it’s just a
долбодят лифта просто Короче просто
bummer to
капец
drink pomp with us, a kilogram straight at a time,
пить пышность нами килограмм прям за раз
autumn and the butt is
осень а попок
even more and more important his YouTube is driving
дуже и дуже важен его YouTube загоняя
us through the cardio-circle into the shadow  ban and even the
нас через кардиорке в теневые бан и дуже
richest person is not shown to people in
богатого виду не показывается людям в
private, information about
частном на показывается информация про
streams is shown, so in order for the little
стримы поэтому для того чтобы мало
operational whistle of the piss right at a time and
оперативный свисток пищица прям за раз а
attempts there in a kilogram about Cream video
попыт там в килограмме о Крим видео
information and we will show you wormwood posts
информация и мы полыни с вами постины
[music]
[музыка]